coming of jesus
by the way
chariots and horsemen represents land
power
the whirlwind represents air power
ships represent sea power
there is a beast from the sea
a beast from the earth
and the power of the print the power the
prince of the power of the air
the threefold union yaw is
apostate protestantism the papacy and
satan himself
when he appears as jesus
listen to what it said by the decree of
enforcing the institution of the papacy
in violation of the law of god our
nation will disconnect herself fully
from righteousness when protestantism
shall stretch her hand across the gulf
to grasp the hand of the roman power
when she shall reach over the abyss to
clasp hands with what
spiritualism went under the influence of
its threefold union our country shall
repudiate every principle of his
constitution as a protestant and
republican government and shall make
provision for the propagation of papal
falsehoods and delusions
then we may know the time has come for
the marvelous working of satan and that
the end is near what kind of a union is
it y'all
threefold it's not just the papacy it's
not just apostate protestantism but it
is spiritualism which is headed up by
satan himself
let me make it even plainer
revelation 13 13 he doeth great wonders
that he caused fire to come down from
heaven on the earth in the sight of men
remember how jesus comes he comes with
what
with fire
this power is going to imitate the
coming of jesus
and watch this it is the miracle working
power
that leads people to create an image to
the beast and all who will not bow down
will work will be killed now please
listen carefully y'all
this hasn't happened yet
and it will not happen until
come on y'all until
[Music]
listen to this
the apostle john
i'm almost done okay i promise you
the apostle john envisioned heard a loud
voice in heaven exclaiming woe to the
inhabiters of the earth and of the sea
for the devil is come down unto you
having great wrath because he knows he
has but a short time there is a time
beloved that the devil is literally
coming to us
pretending to be jesus
because he knows his time is what
and why does he know his time is short
because
the gospel has been preached in all the
world
there's no way for us to know when the
gospel free we just got to preach it
and done he will know satan will know
and god will know our job is to not know
hasn't been done yet our job is to do it
watch
fearful of the scenes which call forth
this exclamation from the heavenly voice
the wrath of satan increases as time
grows short and his work of deceit and
destruction reached its culmination in
the time of trouble now this is from uh
spirit of prophecy volume 4 page 440
page 440 paragraph three i want you to
note i'm reading straight here look at
what happens in the next paragraph as
the crowning act in the great drama of
deception satan himself will attempt to
do what
person a christ the church has long
professed to look to the savior's advent
as the consummation of her hopes now the
great deceiver will make it appear that
christ has come in different parts of
the earth satan will manifest himself
among men as a majestic being of
dazzling brightness resembling the
description of the son of god given by
john in the revelation the glory that
surrounds him is unsurpassed by anything
that mortal eyes have yet behold beheld
the shout of triumph rings out in the
air christ has come christ has come
the people prostrate themselves in
adoration before him while he lifts up
his hands and pronounces a blessing upon
them as christ blessed his disciples
when he was personally upon the earth
his voice is soft and subdued yet full
of melody in gentle compassionate tones
he presents some of the same gracious
heavenly truths which the savior uttered
he heals the diseases of the people and
then
watch this y'all
and then
in his assumed character of christ
he claims to have changed the sabbath to
sunday and commands
let me ask you a question when does this
command to keep sunday holy when does it
happen
does it happen tomorrow
does it happen next week
no when does it happen y'all
after after the gossiping preached
after the abomination of desolation has
been set up
it is
it is satan himself
who convinces atheists
muslims
hindus
agnostics
the whole world
is deceived by this miracle
if you can't get the world to agree on a
vaccine right now
what makes you think that something the
pope says or something some evangelical
says or a global warming or whatever is
going to cause people to come together
and say yeah we need to keep sunday
no y'all that's not happening that only
happens when this happens
let me keep reading
he declares that those who who persist
in keeping holy the seventh day are
blaspheming his name by refusing to
listen to his angels sent to them with
light and truth this is the strong
almost over mastering delusion like the
samaritans who were deceived by simon
magnus the multitudes from the least to
the greatest give heed to these what
give he to these vaccines
come on guys come on
let us be mature seventh-day adventists
give heed to these drugs
give heed to these mental deceptions
y'all
saying this is the great power of god
watch this same reading
spirit of prophecy volume 4 page 4 44
same page watch satan will continue to
act a double part appearing to be the
dispenser of great blessings and divine
truths he will by his lying wonders hold
the world under his control and at the
same time he will indulge his malignity
by causing distress and destruction and
will accuse god's people as the cause of
the fearful convulsions of the nature of
nature and the strife and bloodshed
among men which are desolating the earth
thus will he excite the great intensity
the to greater intensity the spirit of
hatred and persecution against them do
y'all see the order here gospel preached
in all the world abominations of
desolation set up
mark of the beast
it's not the other way around y'all
in the same page in the last conflict
the sabbath will be the special point of
controversy throughout all christendom
secular rulers and religious leaders
will unite to enforce the observance of
sunday and as milder measures fail the
most oppressive laws will be enacted all
of this is happening under satan
appearing as jesus christ
it will be urged that the few who stand
in opposition to to an institution of
the church and law of the church and the
law of the land ought not be tolerated
and a decree will finally be issued
denouncing them as deserving of the
severest punishment and giving the
people liberty after a certain time to
put them to death and notice the next
page the next paragraph the people of
god
will what
flee from the cities and villages
and associate together in companies
dwelling in the most desolate and
solitary do you all see this
she just described to us matthew 24.
not global warming not vaccinations not
global elites
nothing the papacy does
nothing apostate protestantism
these things are are leading somewhere
but it is ultimately satan himself
beloved and that will not happen until
god's people
remember the problem of the ten virgins
five wise five were foolish
the five their light went out they lost
their understanding of prophecy
let me say it again they lost their
understanding of prophecy they may have
been sign hunters
just looking for all kinds of signs and
just disoriented them they became
prophetically crazy
and that's what we're seeing beloved
people are becoming prophetically crazy
looking for signs instead of doing what
god has called us to do y'all
the five foolish virgins they will run
to and fro seeking the word of the lord
and shall not find it because it is too
late
this is my last slide
character is revealed by a what
crisis
when the earnest voice proclaimed at
midnight behold the bridegroom cometh go
ye out to meet him the sleeping virgins
roused from their slumber and it was
seen who had made preparation for the
event listen carefully both parties were
taking what
unawares
why midnight is the darkest night of the
hour midnight is when something happens
that no one was expecting and let me
tell you something beloved there is no
sign
that tells us satan is about to appear
this is why all the virgins were caught
off guard were caught unaware
we are so busy looking for signs to try
to help us to prepare when god is saying
no be ready now
be ready despite what you see going on
be ready now because you don't know when
midnight is going to hit
and how do i be ready now go preach the
gospel
some
sudden or both parties were taken
unawares but one was prepared for the
for the emergency and the other was
found without preparation character is
revealed by circumstances beloved listen
to me we're in the time of the foot man
right now
and and this
crisis we're facing
has revealed a lot of characters
listen
god is trying to wake us up
god is trying to source if y'all are
losing your minds
in the time of the footmen
how you gonna do
when the real thing hits cause this is
not the real thing y'all
we might feel good about ourselves this
is not the thing
when that thing hits it catches
everybody unaware
emergencies bring out the true medal of
character some sudden unlooked for
calamity bereavement or crisis some
unexpected sickness or anguish something
that brings the soul face to face with
death will bring out the true inwardness
of the character it will be made
manifest whether or not there is any
real faith in the promise of the word of
god it will be made manifest whether or
not the soul is sustained by grace
whether there is oil in the vessels with
the lamb beloved how many of you want to
be ready for that time
you know who's going to be ready for
that time those who are doing the work
of god
those who are participating in the
fulfillment of the first angels message
and beloved i'm appealing to you i'm
appealing to the church i'm appealing to
you watching right now
we must
lay aside
the things that divide us and stop
trying
to set ourselves apart as better than
our brother or sister
let us be about our father's business
let us be about the work he's called us
to do the three angels messages must be
fulfilled in order and if the first
angel's message is not fulfilled the
second cannot be fulfilled and the third
cannot be fulfilled but listen y'all it
will be fulfilled
if god has to empty his church if god
has to shake it which he will
it will be fulfilled the only question
is will you be a part of it or will you
be one of those who think in yourself
better than others who thinking yourself
holier than others will you be one of
those who will be shaken out so that
god's church can go forward triumphant
and completing this message
i want you to stand to your feet if
you're saying lord
i want to be one
i want to be among those
who help to complete the first angels
message
beloved we got to do it in a lifetime
you ever thought about that we have to
accomplish this in a lifetime that means
everybody on the planet so we better
start thinking of how
how we do this
how do we do this
we need to put our minds together and
say how are we going to get this gospel
out there like never before what how can
we use technology what can we do how can
we come together and pray together to
accomplish this mission in one
generation it can't be fi it's got to be
one generation because everybody living
at the same time must know the truth at
the same time and either make their
decision for it or against it how we
gonna do that
let's start talking about stuff like
that
let's start talking about how we're
gonna get this message completed instead
of fighting against one another
heavenly father
you've spoken to us
you have shown us the order of events to
take place
please lord
help us to no longer be sign hunters
but help us to look at the signs that
you gave us and there's only two left
one is the preaching of the gospel in
all the world and the second one that
comes after that is the abomination of
desolation being set up those are the
two signs lord and one is out of our
control the other one is totally in our
control
the burden is upon us
teach us to be like the disciples on the
day of pentecost who came together and
prayed for the outpouring of the spirit
so that they could preach the gospel in
the whole then known world
let us be about our father's business
forgive us
for our childishness forgive us
for our foolishness forgive us for our
lukewarmness forgive us for our false
courage and our false bravado forgive us
lord
of our critical spirits
our judgmental spirits
and help us
to fulfill the three angels messages
help us
to survive
the shaking in jesus name we pray amen
and amen
you may be seated
[Music]